Hei, mă auzi?!
Nu-ți da duhul pe aici!
Dacă devine prea greu,
doar du-te unde vezi cu ochii!
Trăiește-ți viața așa cum dorești!
Așa voi face.
Nu am crezut niciodată
că mă voi întoarce aici.
Intră.
Uite-i...
Regina Demon, Echidna,
și cei Patru Mari Generali!
E în regulă. Nu și-au dat seama cine sunt.
Nu încă. Trebuie să mă apropii mai mult...
Closer, now...
'Tis I, former Hero Leo Demonhart!
I'm here to apply for a position in the Demon Army!
Not only am I a skilled swordsman
but I have also mastered all schools of magic!
I even defeated the Demon Queen Echidna herself in single combat!
I am ready and raring to fight for your cause!
And I'm well aware of your army's current situation:
Your severe understaffing has made recovery nigh-impossible!
How do I know this? Because I was the one who decimated your army!
But let's forget the past and look towards the future!
The time has come for a brighter future.
Together, we shall bring ruin to those foolish humans...
and create a glorious Demon Kingdom to last a millennia!
That is why I want to be hired to join your army!
That was perfect. I got this in the bag.
Are you stupid?! Why the hell would we hire you?!
If you hire me, you'll have an incredibly powerful asset—
I'll make you the greatest Demon Queen there ever was!
Why are you still talking?!
I'll help you rapidly grow your workfo—
Shut up!
Under my management, performance will skyrocket, and—
Die!
I'll bring you tea, do all your photocopies!
I'll clean the bathroom!
And if you hire me in the next twenty minutes...
you'll receive a brand-new...
I'd like to take a minute to explain a bit more about myself.
One year ago, the Demon Army, under the leadership of Echidna,
descended upon the human world in a surprise invasion.
His Majesty the King gave me a mission to destroy the Demon Army.
As such, I gathered a party of elite heroes and set out from the capital at once.
There was just one problem.
I don't mean to brag, but I'm really powerful.
As a Royal Knight, I've mastered every weapon and magic known to man.
And to be totally honest, my party members just got in my way.
I had a priestess who refused to learn anything that wasn't a healing spell,
a meathead soldier who didn't know jack about magic,
and an archer who was straight-up useless in close range.
Still, I forged trusting bonds with those dead weights,
defeated our enemies with the power of teamwork and friendship,
and watched them fight about room assignments at every inn we stopped at.
It was so stupid!
I could've saved the world five times over!
Get Hired! Interview Tips and Tricks
So in the end, I set off by myself, defeated Queen Echidna by myself, and decimated the Demon Army by myself!
That's how freakin' strong I am!
There's literally no reason not to hire me!
Perhaps you weren't given a chance because of your demeanor, Master Leo.
But I've turned over a new leaf!
Yeah! He's a totally new leaf!
Quiet down, Lily. Stop jumping.
There's literally no reason not to hire him!
Oh, let her be, Mernes. Lily's just happy to see him again.
I know it's late to be realizing this,
but you've got a real diverse group here.
Just tell us what you want already and make it quick.
If Queen Echidna found out we were meeting with you, she'd burn the castle to the ground.
And we're only meeting with you because you wouldn't stop pestering us,
even after you were thrown out!
All right. Let me start with a little presentation, then.
A present...
I'd like to remind each of you just how powerful I am.
And why would you do that?
I'll admit that my demeanor can be problematic at times.
Even so, the fact that I was strong enough to defeat all four of you solo
should be enough to qualify me for the position.
By reminding each of you how you were defeated,
I hope to gain your endorsement.
What?!
I see! I can most certainly vouch for your skill.
It'd been far too long since someone bested me in a fair duel!
It's not a laughing matter!
Come, now, it's wonderful to cross swords with such a powerful opponent!
Wouldn't you agree, Master Leo?
The first of the Four Generals I fought was this one,
Edvard the Dragon General, a.k.a. "The Red Roar."
In terms of raw stats, he was the toughest one of the bunch.
Dragonfolk and their draconic scales are ridiculously tough.
If I had to fight him just with my sword, who knows how that could have gone.
Luckily for me, he's the kind of idiot—
Er, noble warrior who charges in solo, so the fight was way easier.
Great stuff!
I've a question for you, actually. Why do you serve Echidna, anyway?
You're strong enough to go for world domination.
Why, you ask?
Honestly, I've never given it proper thought.
But I guess it's 'cause I want to live the life of a proper swordsman, dueling strong opponents.
Besides...
Rulin' the world is busy work.
I wouldn't get to spend as much time with my daughter Julietta.
I couldn't bear it, no sir!
I didn't know you have a daughter...
I actually feel quite bad for you.
What? Why?
If you came here alone, then you must not have any friends to spend your time with.
You're one to talk, Mernes.
I'm 100% sure you don't have any friends, either.
After I defeated Edvard, I fought this guy here:
Mernes the Shadowless General, a.k.a. "The Unseen Blade."
Rumors say he's a deadly young half-demon who was once with the Assassin's Guild.
However, when I fought him, his speed and strength were unmatched.
He might have beaten me if he had five more minutes.
Unfortunately for him, I didn't plan on contesting his speed.
I casted Crimson Comet, an AoE spell, to blow him away,
but it ended up destroying everything in its radius, which included the church.
And honestly, I had a rougher time after I'd defeated him.
Apparently the blast was so big, it took out one of the town's historical sites.
What happened after that fight with the townspeople?
Did you ever pay them ba—
Hello hello? I can't hear you! You'll have to speak up!
I can't hear ya! You'll have to speak up!
I'm sorry, Lily, but...
Hey, Leo! Did I sound like you? Did I?
After Mernes came this little surprise.
Lily the Beast General, a.k.a. "The Ruthless Fang."
Our first encounter was completely ridiculous.
I took shelter from the rain under a tree,
and when I looked to the side, she was there, standing next to me.
At the time, she had amnesia, no family, no friends, and nowhere to go.
I wasn't about to leave a little kid out there alone, so I took care of her for a few days.
But then she remembered who she was, and she introduced herself as the Beast General Lily. Great.
I had to fight her eventually, so I fought her. Of course, I won.
Pretty, uh, easily...
Later, I learned that in their tribe, if someone strong defeats you in combat,
they're the person you're destined to be with.
Why'd this have to happen to me?
Hey, Leo! When're you gonna marry me? C'mon, marry me!
Maybe when you're just a little older.
I don't wanna wait! I wanna marry you now! Right now!
And finally, I fought Shutina the Sorcerer General, a.k.a. "The Almighty Mage."
People say that she had a far greater pool of mana than other succubi,
and had mastered all types of sorcery, including ancient and accursed.
Knowing that, I started our battle with the AoE spell Stasis, which prevents spellcasting altogether,
and challenged her in physical combat.
She was... embarrassingly weak.
After two minutes, you started crying for mercy. It's kinda sad, really.
I'm a mage! Of course I'm no match in hand-to-hand combat!
Sure, but a real professional would have a plan B.
How am I supposed to have a plan B for someone who can nullify all my spells?!
There literally isn't anyone in the world who can do that the second they walk up!
Except there is: me.
Forget that! What is all this about, anyway?!
I told you I was gonna give you a presentation.
I admit, I did want to hear how he defeated the rest of you.
It all happened so fast.
Agreed!
I was curious, too!
And you were by far the most useless of all of us, Shutina.
Agreed!
Poor Shutina!
Will you just get to the point already?!
Why did you, a hero, come to interview for a job with the Demon Army?
That's what I want to know!
Why do you even want to join the Demon Army?!
I didn't come here to mess with you.
I'll answer your question.
I'll tell you why I left my life of fighting the Demon Army behind,
and why I decided to defect to your side after so long.
So listen up.
After defeating the four of you and Echnida herself, I returned to Renailles.
But there was no celebration or cheering to be heard.
Instead, I was met with long stares and sharp glares filled with shock, fear, and skepticism.
Is he really human?!
No, he's a monster in human clothing!
Oh, crap!
The fear and worry spread like wildfire. I couldn't stop it.
Word spread via letter, messenger pigeon, magic, and posters:
"The Hero Leo is a danger to us all."
We cannot allow that man to wander free through our streets!
We cannot let him wreck havoc upon us. We must put an end to that man— No, that monster!
He's right! Kill him!
I was the new evil to be killed. That was what humanity came to believe.
In the following days, I was accosted by assassins.
I couldn't believe their stupidity! I took out the Demon Queen all by myself!
Did they really think I'd let some half-rate assassins do me in?!
Some time after that, I was called to the palace to speak with the King.
It was your actions that kept the Philosopher's Stone safe, and for that, I thank you.
It pains me to make this decree,
but as the kingdom's protector, I cannot turn a blind eye to the concerns of my people.
Great Hero Leo,
I hereby sentence you to exile.
Very well.
Never forget, though,
that I have the utmost trust in your goodwill.
Why did I risk my life to protect this rotten world?
Why did I fight tooth and nail against the Demon Army?
Everything was suddenly so meaningless.
I never had a home, so I had nowhere to go.
All I could do was wander aimlessly from village to village.
Then, one day...
Did you hear what the Demon Army's doing?
Yeah, they're recruiting, right? Can you believe it?
They're actually trying to do it again, after getting their asses handed to them by that hero.
You'd think they learned their lesson.
That Demon Queen Echidna isn't the sharpest tool in the shed, is she?
Echidna...
Sure isn't. Only a matter of time before we stop hearin' about her.
Yep.
Echidna, huh?
What happened to that thing'a yours?
I don't know why...
But I concluded that the only place willing to take me in
was the Demon Army itself.
So I stayed up all night working on my spiel,
putting together a fancy presentation,
and I crossed the endless sands,
scaled the treacherous mountains,
all to arrive here.
If the world is hellbent on killing me, then I just have to kill them first.
And that's why I want to work for you.
Very well, Leo the Hero.
You poor, pitiful soul, who devoted his heart and body to the wrong people.
I sense no falsehoods nor trickery behind your reasons to join with us.
I believe you are genuine.
Thank you, Sorcerer General Shutina.
I've definitely gotten over a big hurdle here.
However...
You will be subjected to a one-month trial period!
I'll be your manager for that period, and will evaluate your worthiness!
I expect you to produce results during your trial period.
And if those results are unsatisfactory?
Then we'll throw you out!
I'll work hard. I'm pretty done with roughing it out there.
And you must not let Queen Echidna know we've hired you at all.
Use a magic item or spell to keep yourself disguised at all times.
You got it. So, are there any issues you've been dealing with as of late?
Our top priorities are bolstering our ranks, repairing the castle, and procuring weapons.
After that, there's budgeting, improving employee benefits, and providing counseling...
We also need to perform maintenance on the mana reactors, train any new recruits...
Rebuilding an army is a lot of work!
And not just for Shutina!
I've got a lotta work to do, too, y'know!
Stop jumping, Lily.
I've been helping with loj... lojistics?
Like, getting supplies and stuff, and it's been really hard!
There's so much I gotta do!
What? You can't be serious!
You know logistics is...
the most important part of any...
That's right! It's the most important, and they asked me to do it!
Isn't that amazing? It's amazing!
Sheesh, it's even worse than I thought.
Whoa! Watch it!
This is all your fault!
Calm down there, Shutina.
You've gotta admit, it'd be a relief to have Master Leo on our side.
I suppose, but still...
No!
Very well. I can be calm. I'm calm, yes...
Okay, let's let bygones be bygones! Glad to have ya, Master Leo!
Glad to have ya!
Same here. Thanks, Edvard. You too, Lily.
Hey, Mernes. You good? I'm looking forward to working with you, too.
Leo the Hero.
If you can produce good results during this trial period,
we will not cheapen your efforts by bringing you in as an 'unpaid intern.'
We, the Four Great Generals, will recommend to Queen Echidna that you be officially taken in.
I won't let you down, I promise.
They're in dire need of people, especially those skilled in management.
Then those bolstered ranks need training. There's a lot of tasks on the table.
They're essentially rebuilding from zero.
They're not just struggling; they're on the brink of closing up shop.
But that's exactly why I need to talk to Echidna,
and ask her the question I've been pondering since that day.
What are you doing?!
Q-Queen Echidna!
You heard my orders!
While this is an invasion, we must not kill whenever possible!
Any territory we occupy must be ruled peacefully!
She forbids indiscriminate killing.
What cause is so important that she would handicap her army like that?
Why does she still refuse to leave the human world despite her utter defeat?
I need to ask her these questions and more.
Live your life the way you want!
Just you watch, Echidna. I'll be a part of your army before you know it.
This is the story of how I did just that.
Episodul 1: Următorul meu interviu de la Castelul Reginei Demon
Trăiește, trăiește, continuă să trăiești
și să urmezi lumina spre viitor
Renunț să mai fiu erou!
Trădat și abandonat în această lume singuratică,
Temându-mă de ziua de mâine, pe care am scăpat-o din vedere,
Continui să caut locul unde aparțin
Inima mea strigă: „Vreau ca lumea să aibă nevoie de mine”
Vreau să deslușesc aceste personalități întortocheate,
dar oare chiar mă pot încrede în ele?
Trăiește, trăiește, continuă să trăiești
și să urmezi lumina spre viitor
Chiar dacă vei pierde totul,
păstrează-ți măcar speranța vie în suflet
Chiar dacă nu știu de ce sunt aici,
sunt în regulă cu asta
Deoarece trebuie să depășesc orice obstacol îmi va ieși în cale,
ca să pot zâmbi alături de tine din nou
Data viitoare
Dă tot ce poți acum ca ziua de mâine să-ți fie mai ușoară